

# Jessica Rodriguez



## **About me**

Experienced digital and fine artist with five years of commission experience and two years of professional experience, including both digital and physical design, animation, and team management. Seeking an opportunity to utilize my unique style, passion for art, and collaborative management abilities.

## www.jessarod.com (814) 826 - 8109 jess@yasfu.net

3365 Delaney Dr Melbourne, FL 32934



# **Education**

## **Penn State University**

Bachelors in Digital Arts & Media Design, Minor in Architectural Studies, Minor in Art 2017 - 2022

Thesis: Developmental Dioramas in Design: Understanding digital spaces through physical models.

## **Skills**

(Spanish and French)

Adobe Creative Suite
(Photoshop, InDesign,
Illustrator)
Composition
Concept Art
Design Principles
Modeling & Rendering
Team Management
Trilingual

## **Experience**

### **Graphic Designer**

Embraer - Melbourne, FL 2023 - Present Web Design

### **Disney College Program**

The Walt Disney Company - Lake Buena Vista, FL 2022 - 2023

Customer service upholding Disney values

#### **Art Instructor**

**PSU Center for Arts & Crafts** - University Park, PA 2021 - 2022

Planned and led multiple weekly classes Wood-burning, Drawing, Ink & Colored Pencil, Pastels

#### **Graphic Design Intern**

**PSU Viral Imaginations** - University Park, PA 2021 - 2022

Graphic Design for posters, flyers, and business cards Curated submissions contributed to the online gallery